<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="pretty-atom-feed.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>pawn002&#39;s Blog</title>
  <subtitle>Design integration, accessibility advocacy, and ethical AI strategy</subtitle>
  <link href="https://pawn002.github.io/blog/feed/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://pawn002.github.io/blog/blog-public/" />
  <updated>2025-10-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://pawn002.github.io/blog/blog-public/</id>
  <author>
    <name>John Rioflorido</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Legal Disclaimer</title>
    <link href="https://pawn002.github.io/blog/blog/legal_disclaimer/" />
    <updated>2025-10-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://pawn002.github.io/blog/blog/legal_disclaimer/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The content provided on this blog is for informational purposes only and does not constitute professional advice. While every effort is made to ensure the accuracy and reliability of the information presented, the author makes no warranties regarding its completeness or suitability for any particular purpose. Readers are encouraged to seek professional guidance for specific issues or decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any opinions expressed in this blog are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the views of affiliated organizations or institutions. The author is not responsible for any loss or damage arising from reliance on the information contained herein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, comments and discussions generated on this blog may contain views or opinions from third parties, which do not necessarily align with the author&#39;s perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By reading this blog, you acknowledge and accept these terms.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Good Day to All!</title>
    <link href="https://pawn002.github.io/blog/blog/firstpost/" />
    <updated>2025-10-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://pawn002.github.io/blog/blog/firstpost/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome the blog!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site is very much under construction, so this post is a shortie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of upheaval across diverse domains right now. I find spaces like this present a rich opportunity space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a lot to say on upheaval and opportunuity, but I have a blog site to build out. 😉&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please stay tuned for writing that touches on opportunity and many other subjects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you in the next post(s)!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>